Guide to the Elmer J. Holland Papers, 1937-1968 AIS.1968.23
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Legislative Files, II.
  - Legislation Introduced, 1.
    - H.R. 8399- Occupational Training and Manpower Utilization, July 31, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - H.R. 8420- Private Bill for the Relief of Cecylia Orszula Pulit, July 31, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - H.R. 8777-Private Bill for Relief of Lt. Liu Ching Chiu, His Spouse, and Minor Child, August 17, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - H.R. 9540- Postal Pay Raise, January 11, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - H.R. 9694- To Amend Social Security Act to Include PA among States which May Obtain SS coverage for State and Local Policemen and Fireman, January 16, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - H.R. 9713- Private Bill for Relief of Michalina Adela Chudziak, January 16, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - H.R. 10055- Federal Employees Pay Raise, February 5, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - H.R. 10149- Relief of Mrs. An Fu Wang Lee, February 7, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - H.R. 10959- Relief of John and Ann Beg Farkas, March 27, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - H.R. 11210- Relief of Donato Panella, April 10, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - H.R. 11680- Amend NDEA to Include Program to Improve School Library Resources Needed for Teaching and Learning, May 9, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - H.R. 11785- Mass Transportation Legislation, May 16, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - H.R. 11786- Retirement Legislation (Forgotten Widows), May 16, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - H.R. 11787- Amend C.S. Retirement Act, May 16, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - H.R. 12099- Private Bill for the Relief of Mrs. Zorka Boskov, June 12, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - H.R. 12374- Relief of Dung How Yee & Yai Suey Yee, June 29, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - H.R. 12729- Provides for a Set Date for Primary Elections in All States, July 21, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - H.R. 12456- To Amend Manpower Development and Training Act of 1962, July 11, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - H.R. 12793- To Authorize Modification of Local Participation in Flood Control Projects, August 7, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - H.R. 12866- Relief of George Sakellariou, August 9, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - H.J. Res. 898- To Provide for Three Civilian Commissioners for the District of Columbia, September 9, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - H.R. 1501- Private Bill Relief of Lt. Liu Ching Chiu, January 9, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - H.R. 1500- Private Bill Relief of Mrs. An Fu Wang Lee, January 9, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - H.R. 1499- Private Bill Relief of John and Ann Beg Farkas, January 9, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - H.R. 1498- Relief of Mrs. Zorka Boskov, January 9, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - H.R. 1497- Relief of Dung How Yee and Kai Suey Yee, January 9, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - H.R. 1496- Relief of George Sakellariou, January 9, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - H.R. 890- Provide Primary Elections and Runoff Primary Elections to be Held on Same Day Throughout the Nation, January 9, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - H.R. 774- Mass Transportation Bill, January 9, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - H.R. 774- Provide 1-year Moratorium on Principal Payments under FHA & VA mortgages for Unemployed, January 9, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - H.R. 629- Amend National Defense Education Act to Provide Program to Improve School Library Resources, January 9, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - H.R. 628- Allow Railroad Employees to Retire on Full Annuity at Age 60 After 30 Years of Service, January 9, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - H.R. 627- Allow Deduction for Tuition and Other Educational Expense, January 9, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - H.R. 355- To Reduce Maximum Work-Week to 32 hours. Amend Fair Labor Standards Act, January 9, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - H.R. 354- Amend Coal Mine Safety Act to Remove Exemption with Respect to Certain Mines Employing No More than 14 Individuals, January 9, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - H.R. 353- Amend Coal Mine Safety Act to Provide Further for Prevention of Accidents in Coal Mines, January 9, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - H.R. 95- Payment of Pensions to WWI Veterans, January 9, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - H.R. 94- Benefits for Peacetime Veterans, January 9, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - H.R. 57- Prevent Use of Stopwatches or Other Measuring Devices in Postal Service, January 9, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - H.R. 56- Increase Income Tax Exemptions from $600 to $1000, January 9, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - H.R. 55- Unemployment Reinsurance Grants to States, to Revise, Extend & Improve Unemployment Insurance Program, January 9, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - H.R. 54- To Allow Income Tax Deduction for Dependent Expenses for College and University, January 9, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - H.R. 53- Medical Care for the Elderly Under Social Security (Forand Bill), January 9, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - H. Con. Res. 16- Create Joint Committee on National Fuels Study, January 9, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - H.J. Res. 91- Provide 3 Civilian Commissioners for D.C., January 9, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - H.J. Res. 90- Designate March 20 as "Shut In's Day", January 9, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - H.R. 1800- Certificate of Rehabilitation on Proof of Exemplary Conduct in Civilian Life in Cases of Discharges other than Honorable, January 14, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - H.R. 1801- Prohibit Issuance of Discharges Other than Honorable except pursuant to sentence of a Court Martial, January 14, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - H.R. 1802- Repeal of Section 14(b) of the National Labor Relations Act, January 14, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - H.R. 2672- Relief of Boro of Port Vue, January 24, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - H.R. 2879- Amends Sec. 2(2) of NLR Act, January 28, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - H.R. 3087- Social Security Amendments, January 31, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - H.R. 3518- Amend Sec. 9(b)(3) of NLR Act- Eliminate Provision Prohibiting Certification as Bargaining Rep. of Guards in Labor Organizations, February 7, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - H.R. 3519- Provide Annuities Payable from Civil Service Retirement by Eliminating "5-Year" Provision "Forgotten Widows", February 7, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - H.R. 3520- Amend Title II of SS Act & to Provide Child's Insurance Benefits to Continue after 18 or until Completion of High School, February 7, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - H.R. 3773- To Establish a Youth Conservation Corps., February 14, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - H.R. 3815- Amend Sec. 8(b)(4) of NLR Act (Situs Picketing), February 14, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - H.R. 4033- Prohibit Discrimination in Payment of Wages Because of Sex, February 21, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - H.R. 5868- To Provide Federal Financial Assistance for Construction & Expansion of Public Jr. Col., April 25, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - H.R. 6472- Relief of Mrs. Ourania Thomareis, May 21, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - H.R. 6991- Amend Manpower Development and Training Act. Delete Sec 203(d), June 12, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - H.R. 7000- Amend Manpower Development & Training Act- Sec. 202, etc, June 12, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - H. R. 7277- Amend Manpower Dev. & Tr. Act, July 2, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - H.R. 7993- Relief of Kevork Agopoglu, August 7, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - H.J. Res 663- Equal Rights for Men and Women, August 22, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - H.R. 8236- For the Relief of Felippo & Giuseppa Raccuglia and minor children Antonino and Tommaso, August 23, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - H.R. 8419- Manpower Bill, September 12, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - H.R. 8720- Amend Manpower Act, October 7, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - H.R. 9136- For Relief of Maria Giurlani, November 14, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - H.R. 10310- To Establish a National Commission on Automation & Technological Progress, March 10, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - H.R. 11611- Establish National Commission on Technology, Automation, & Economic Progress, June 16, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - H.R. 11821- Provide for Issuance of a Special 50 cent Piece in Honor of each of the several States, June 29, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - H.R. 11828- For the Relief of Esther Robbins- Private Bill, June 29, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - H.R. 11976- To Encourage the Training of Employment Counselors, July 21, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - H.R. 12786- "Employment Act Amendments of 1964", October 2, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - H.R. 1540- Prohibit Discharge of Members of Armed Forces under Conditions Other than Honorable except pursuant to Sentence of Court Martial, January 5, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - H.R. 1541- Amend Chapter 79 of Title 10, U.S. Code- Authorize Boards to Give Consideration to Exemplary Conduct, etc., January 5, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - H.R. 1542- To Amend the National Labor Relations Act, January 5, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - H.R. 1543- To Repeal Section 14(b) of the National Labor Relations Act, January 5, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - H.R. 1544- To Amend the Federal Coal Mine Safety Act to Provide Further Prevention of Accidents, January 5, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - H.R. 1545- To Amend Fair Labor Standards Act to Extend Protection to Additional Employees, January 5, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - H.R. 1546- To Reduce Maximum Workweek under Fair Labor Standards Act to 32 Hours, January 5, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - H.R. 1547- To Provide for the Establishment of the National Humanities Foundation, January 5, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - H.R. 1548- To Amend Sec. 9(b)(3) of Nat. Labor Relations Act to Eliminate Provision Prohibiting Certification as Bargaining Reps., January 5, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - H.R. 1549- To Provide that Primary Elections & Runoff Primary Elections to be Held on Same Day Throughout U.S., January 5, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - H.R. 1550- Railroad Employees to Retire on Full Annuity at Age 60 or after 30 Years Service, January 5, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - H.R. 1551- Amend Title 18 of U.S. Code to Make it a Federal Crime to Kill the President of the U.S., January 5, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - H.R. 1552- Prevent Use of Stopwatches or Other Measuring Devices in Postal Service, January 5, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - H.R. 1553- Amend Title 38 of U.S. to Provide for Payment of Pensions to Veterans of WWI, January 5, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - H.R. 1554- Benefits for Peacetime Veterans, January 5, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - H.R. 1555- Amend Internal Revenue Code to Allow Deductions for Education Purposes, January 5, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - H.R. 1556- To Increase Income Tax Deduction from $600 to $1000, January 5, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - H.R. 1557- Amend Internal Revenue Code to Allow Deduction for College Expenses, January 5, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - H.R. 1558- Amend Title II of Social Security Act- Increase Benefits at age 60, etc, January 5, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - H.R. 1600- Private Bill for Relief of Lt. Liu Ching Chiu, his spouse, and minor child, January 5, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - H.R. 1601- Private Bill for Relief of Kevork Agopoglu, January 5, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - H.R. 1602- Private Bill for Relief of Mrs. Zorka Boskov, January 5, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - H.R. 1603- Private Bill for Relief of George Sakellariou, January 5, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - H.R. 1604- Private Bill for Relief of Dung How Yee and Kai Suey Yee, January 5, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - H.R. 1605- Private Bill for Relief of Esther Robbins, January 5, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - H.R. 1606- Private Bill for Relief of Maria Giurlani, January 5, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - H.R. 1607- Private Bill for Relief of Felippo & Giuseppa Raccuglia & minor children, January 5, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - H.R. 1608- Private Bill for Relief of Mrs. Ourania Thomareis... Ltr. to Committee to Table due to death, January 5, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - H.R. 1609- Private Bill for Relief of Mrs. An Fu Wang Lee, January 5, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - H.R. 1701- To Amend Sec. 8(b)(4) of the National Labor Relations Act, January 5, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - H.R. 1813- Amend SS Act to Provide Hospital Insurance (Medicare), January 5, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - H.J. Res. 116 Equal Rights for Men and Women, January 5, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - H.J. Res. 117- Provide 3 Civilian Commissioners for Dist. of Columbia, January 5, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - H.J. Res. 118- Amend Constitution of U.S. on Presidential Power and Succession, January 5, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - H.R. 2435- To Amend NLR Act to Make Provisions Applicable to Agriculture (Migratory Lab), January 12, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - H.R. 2436- Authorize Sec. Labor to Develop & Maintain Voluntary Methods of Recruiting, etc, Agriculture Workers (Migratory Labor), January 12, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - H.R. 2437- To Provide for Establishment of "National Advisory Council on Migratory Labor", January 12, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - H.R. 2438- To Amend Fair Labor Standards Act to Extend Child Labor to Certain Children Employed in Agri (Migratory Labor), January 12, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - H.R. 2439- To Amend Fair Labor Standards Act to Provide Minimum Wage to Certain Persons Employed in Agri. (Migratory Labor), January 12, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - H.R. 2440- Repeal Sec. 14(b) and Amend Sec. 8(a)93) of NLR Act, and Amend Sec. 705(b) of Labor-Management Reporting & Disclosure, January 12, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - H.J. Res. 217- Designating March 30 as "Shut-In Day", January 21, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - H.R. 3937- "Forgotten Widows" Bill- Civil Service Annuities for Widows Whose Husbands Died prior to 1948, and They had not been married 5 Years, February 1, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - H.R. 4257- Amendments to the MDTA, as amended, February 3, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - H.R. 4257- Original Bill As Amended to House Blue Sheets House Report 70, February 3, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - H. Con. Res. 199- Freedom of Religion for All People (Persecution of Jews in Russia), February 4, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - H.J. Res. 835- To Declare May 29 in each Year as Kennedy's Bd. Which Shall be a Legal Public Holiday, February 15, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - H.R. 6191- To Establish National Foundation on the Arts and Humanities, March 11, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - H.J. Res. 977- Proposes National Policy on Education, March 23, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - H.J. Res. 423- Amendment to Constitution, Providing 4-Year Term to House Members, April 5, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - H.J. Res. 1042- To Create a Delegation to a Convention of North Atlantic Nations, April 6, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - H.R. 9766- A Bill to Establish a Federal Sabbatical Program to Improve Quality of Teaching the Nations Elementary or Secondary Schools, July 12, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - H.R. 8387- Amend the Fair Labor Standards Act (Minimum Wage), May 24, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - H.R. 9133- Amend "Act to Promote Safety of Employees & Travelers upon Railroads by Limiting Hours of Service of Employees", June 17, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - H.R. 9227- "Equal Employment Opportunity Act", June 21, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - H.R. 9887- To Provide Fellowships for Graduate Study Leading to Masters or Doctor Degrees for Elementary and Secondary School Teachers and Those who Train Such Teachers, July 15, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - H.R. 9925- Establishment of the National Foundation on Arts & The Humanities, July 19, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - H.R. 10068- To Provide Fellowships for Elementary & Secondary School Personnel, etc, July 26, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - H.R. 10624- To Establish a National Commission on Older Workers, August 25, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - H.R. 10869- Private Bill for the Relief of Jadwiga Dednarska, September 2, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - H.R. 11085- To Amend Welfare & Pension Plans Disclosure Act, September 25, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - H.R. 11164- To Authorize Sec. of Interior to Enlarge and Improve Research Facility near Bruceton, PA, September 20, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - H.R. 11577- Amend F.L.S. Act- 3 Weeks Paid Vacation, October 13, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - H.R. 11703- "Employment Act Amendments of 1965", October 20, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - H.R. 11991- Provide Fed. Assistance to Elementary Schools Thru Services of Child Development Specialists, January 12, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - H.R. 12093- To Amend Internal Revenue Code with Regard to Private Pension Funds, January 17, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - H.R. 12820- Self-Supporting Reinsurance Program to Protect Employees Under Private Pension Plans, February 15, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - H.R. 13037- Manpower Services Act of 1966, February 24, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - H.R. 13362- "The Employment Service Act of 1966" to Amend to Wagner-Peyser Act, March 7, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - H.R. 14083- To Provide for Improved Employee-Management Relations in Federal Service, etc, March 29, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - H.R. 14685- Amend MDTA to Provide for Older Workers, April 27, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - H.R. 14690- Amendments to MDTA, April 27, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - H.R. 15291- To Authorize Award of Exemplary Rehabilitation Certificates, etc., May 25, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - H.R. 16715- To Amend the Manpower Development and Training Act of 1962 "MDTA Amendments of 1966", July 29, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - H.R. 17096- To Amend the Internal Revenue Code of 1954 to Exclude from Income Certain Reimbursed Moving Expenses, August 16, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - H.R. 17138- To Improve the Operation of the Legislative Branch of the Federal Govt and for Other Purposes, August 18, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - H.R. 17282- Amends the Railroad Retirement Act of 1937 (Re Social Security Minimum Guaranty Provision), August 25, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - H.R. 17299- Allows Deductions for Teachers for Expenses Incurred in Pursuing Courses for Academic Credit, August 25, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - H.R. 17368- Amend Internal Revenue Code with Respect to Business Development Corps., August 26, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - H.R. 17395- Provides Compensation to Survivors of Local Law Enforcement Officers Killed While Apprehending Persons for Committing Federal Crimes, August 29, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - H.R. 48- To Repeal Section 14(b) of the N.L.R.A., January 10, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - H.R. 49- To Amend Section 8(b)(4) of the N.L.R.A.- "Situs Picketing", January 10, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - H.J. Res. 113- To Propose an Amendment to the Constitution Providing that M.C. Terms be Extended to 4 Years, January 10, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - H.R. 171- To Establish a National Commission on Older Workers, January 10, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - H.R. 683- To Provide Compensation to Survivors of Law Enforcers in Line of Duty Regarding Federal Crimes, January 10, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - H.R. 684- To Provide for Compensation of Persons Injured by Certain Criminal Acts, January 10, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - H.R. 685- To Amend Title II of the Social Security Act Reducing from 60 to 50 Widow's Insurance Benefits, January 10, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - H.R. 686- To Establish a Self-Supporting Federal Reinsurance Program, January 10, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - H.R. 687- To Amend the Internal Revenue Code- Income Tax Treatment of Business Development Corporations, January 10, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - H.R. 688- To Amend the Internal Revenue Code- Pension Plans Which are Correlated with Social Security, January 10, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - H.R. 689- To Exclude from Income Certain Moving Expenses, January 10, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - H.R. 690- D.C. Home Rule, January 10, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - H.R. 691- To Enlarge and Improve Research Facility near Bruceton, PA, January 10, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - H.R. 692- To Amend Welfare and Pension Plans Disclosure Act, January 10, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - H.R. 693- Protection Against Political Activities in Federal Elections, January 10, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - H.R. 694- To Amend United States Code Regarding Pensions to World War I Veterans, January 10, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - H.R. 1996- To Establish the National Advisory Council on Migratory Labor, January 11, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - H.R. 1997- Regarding the Methods of Recruiting, Training, Transporting, etc, of Agricultural Workers, January 11, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - H.R. 1998- To Amend the Internal Revenue Code to Encourage Construction of Housing Facilities for Agriculture Workers, January 11, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - H.R. 1999- To Amend N.L.R.A. so as to Make its Provisions Applicable to Agriculture Workers, January 11, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - H.R. 2000- To Amend F.L.S.A. to Extend the Child Labor Provisions to Children Employed in Agriculture, January 11, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - H.R. 3063- To Amend the Internal Revenue Code with Respect to Educational Expenses, January 19, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - H.R. 3252- To Amend the Disaster Relief Act of 1966 to Provide a National Program of Flood Insurance, January 23, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - H.R. 3768- To Prohibit Age Discrimination in Employment, January 25, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - H.R. 3769- To Amend Social Security Regarding the Reduction in Disability Benefits which is Required where an Individual Gets Workmen's Compensation, January 25, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - H.R. 4337- Eliminate Percentage Depletion Method for Determining Deduction for Depletion of Oil and Gas Wells, January 31, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - H.R. 4482- Provide Equitable System for Fixing & Adjusting Rates of Compensation of Wage Board Employees, February 1, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - H.R. 4730- Survivor Annuity if Predeceased by Person Named Survivor, February 2, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - H.R. 4731- Rates of Postage on Third-Class Mail by Certain NonProfit Organizations, February 2, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - H.R. 4732- Forgotten Widow, February 2, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - H.R. 4733- Health Benefits Pursuant to Elect Coverage under the Retired Federal Employees Health Act of 1960, February 2, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - H.R. 4734- To Modify the Decrease in Federal Group Life Insurance at Age 65 or After Retirement, February 2, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - H.R. 4735- To Equalize Civil Service Retirement Annuities, February 2, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - H.R. 4736- To Provide Annuities for Surviving Spouse Without Deduction from a Retired Employee's Annuity, February 2, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - H.R. 4737- To Amend Internal Revenue Code Whereby first $5000 Received as Annuity be not Considered Income, February 2, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - H.R. 4738- To Provide that Value of Survivor Annuities Shall not be Taxed for Inheritance Purposes, February 2, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - H.J. Res. 317- Proposing Amendment to Const. Relative to Equal Employment for Men and Women, February 20, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - H.R. 5922- To Allow a Tax Deduction from Gross Income for Tuition & Other Educational Expenses, February 21, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - H.R. 5923- To Increase from $600 to $1000 Personal Income Tax Exemption of a Taxpayer, February 21, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - H.R. 6806- Establish Federal Sabbatical Leave Program for Elementary and Secondary Teachers, March 9, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - H.R. 7495- Amends the Older Americans Act of 1965, March 20, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - H.R. 8314- The Economic Opportunity Amendments of 1967, April 10, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - H.R. 8952- To Exclude U.S. Rt. 22 from Haafsville to Easton, PA from the Interstate System, April 20, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 18)